{
    "subject": "resource/Ollie_Cahill",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Footballer",
    "human_readable": "Ollie Cahill is a footballer.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9286810755729675,
            "question": "Is Ollie Cahill a professional athlete?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7856461405754089,
            "question": "What teams has Ollie Cahill played for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7847244143486023,
            "question": "Does Ollie Cahill play any other sports besides football?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7750124335289001,
            "question": "What sport does Ollie Cahill play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7175307273864746,
            "question": "Where is Ollie Cahill from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6935798525810242,
            "question": "In what leagues might Ollie Cahill play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5968962907791138,
            "question": "What position does Ollie Cahill likely play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.437929630279541,
            "question": "Is Ollie Cahill known for any specific skills or abilities?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3684397339820862,
            "question": "Has Ollie Cahill won any awards or trophies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2118457555770874,
            "question": "What is another term for footballer?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ollie Cahill is a footballer.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4842_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Ollie Cahill won any awards or trophies?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4842_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Ollie Cahill known for any specific skills or abilities?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4842_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What position does Ollie Cahill likely play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4842_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4842_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4842_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4842_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4842_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4842_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4842_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4842_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4842_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4842_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4842_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can provide the following response:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThis is because the documents mention Ollie Cahill as a former football player who has played for various League of Ireland teams and has achieved significant success in his career. The documents also mention him playing against Cork City in the FAI Cup, which further supports his role as a footballer."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that Ollie Cahill is a footballer. The context mentions his long career in football, achievements such as winning multiple league winners\u2019 medals, and his roles within football organizations like PFA Ireland."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}